https://www.journalism.co.uk/privacy-policy/s125/

Recruiter login
Latest jobs (All)
Latest jobs (US)
Jobseeker login
Latest jobs (All)
Latest jobs (US)
twitter
Latest Jobs:
Privacy policy
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information(1) What information do we collect?We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views);(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including advertising in our directory of freelance journalists, advertising vacancies on our jobs board, training course bookings and display advertising);(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including registration with our bulletin board, our links directory, our blogs and for the purpose of posting press releases, placing recruitment adverts, submitting tips, posting items to our full-time and short course sections and gaining a listing in our freelance directory);(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including our daily email newsletter, email notifications of job vacancies and notifications of our training courses);(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.(2) Cookies A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. We use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and keep you logged in to administrative areas of the site. We will use the persistent cookies to remember your display preferences.Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users
based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.  (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.(3) Using your personal dataPersonal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.We may use your personal information to:(a) administer the website;(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;(h) send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);(i) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;(j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, WorldPay. You should only provide your personal information to WorldPay after reviewing the WorldPay privacy policy (available at http://worldpay.com/about_us/index.php?page=privacy&c=UK). We will share information with  WorldPay only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.(4) DisclosuresWe may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.In addition, we may disclose information about you: (a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.(5) International data transfers Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States, Canada, Japan, New Zealand and Australia) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area. In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.(6) Security of your personal dataWe will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers.Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.(7) Policy amendments We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. (8) Your rightsYou may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email  at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)(9) Third party websitesThe website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.(10) Updating informationPlease let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.(11) ContactIf you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to info (at) journalism.co.uk or by post to Mousetrap Media Ltd, 100 North Road, Brighton, East Sussex BN1 1YE United Kingdom. (12) Data controllerThe data controller responsible for our website is Mousetrap Media Ltd.  Our data protection registration number is PZ563100X.
Job Alerts
Sign up to receive job alerts of your choice by email, or manage your subscription
Register
Login
Editorial training
rss
twitter
31/12/20
Writing for women's magazines
31/12/20
Digital audience and content editor
Newsquest is looking for a digital audience and content editor to serve multiple news websites in Lancashire and Greater Manchester
Featured jobs
Digital audience and content editor - Newsquest
Digital content editor
- CLA
Digital content editor - Midland News Association
Multimedia reporter - Newsquest
Head of boroughs news - Reach plc
Go to the jobs board
Free daily newsletter
Subscribe to our newsletter for latest news, tips, jobs and more
PressGo: our press release distribution service
View more than 15,000 releases
PR of the week
Stop The Spread Solutions offers the only touchless PPE vending machine
Stop The Spread Solutions begins its first installations of touchless vending machines designed for use in high-traffic public areas where the use of personal protective equipment (PPE) is required
Featured PRs from PressGo
Stop The Spread Solutions offers the only touchless PPE vending machine
Convosphere's head of insights Oliver Lewis to speak at Market Research Society's data analytics event
Twelve times international bestselling author Steven Kotler releases podcast on how to access the flow state
EU isolationism leaving dangerous power vacuum in Balkans, warns major new report on the arms trade
New world's first multi-vitamin and mineral CBD sparkling water launched By Calm Drinks
Go to PressGo
Advertise here: Contact
John Thompson
Newsrewired conference
Online every Tuesday and Thursday 1 to 10 December 2020.
Need freelance help?
End that deadline stress today and find help in our freelance directory
Get the knowledge
Five tips from The Economist to perfect your newsletter strategy
Here is how to craft emails that will keep audiences informed but not overwhelmed
Seven tips for journalism students to ace their virtual courses
University is going to be a bit different this year. Here is how to get the most of Zoom lectures
Eight ways to nail climate emergency reporting
Environmental topics are complicated beats to cover. Here is how to keep readers engaged and your coverage accurate
Seven new journalism podcasts to help you get through the pandemic
Stuck inside and in need of inspiration? Check out these new shows
Mousetrap Media Ltd - info (at) journalism.co.uk tel: +44 1273 384293
